<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
		<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
			<channel>
				<title>RealClearPolitics - Articles</title>
				<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/</link>
				<description></description>
				<language>en</language>
				<copyright>Copyright 2008</copyright>			
				<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 08:22:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
				<generator>http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/?v=3.33</generator>
				<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
				<image>
					<url>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/images/RCP-HOME-WIDE.png</url>
					<title>Real Clear Politics</title>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com</link>
				 </image>
				<item>
					<title>Feeling Powerless All Around</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ The late Katharine Graham was often called one of the most powerful women in the world. You can see why. She controlled The Washington Post, Newsweek, a bevy of television stations and was Washington&apos;s pre-eminent hostess, gathering the influential or the merely interesting in her Georgetown home. Yet she knew her power was severely limited. On a given day, she wouldn&apos;t even dare stop her own newspaper from savaging one of her friends.
What brings this to mind is &quot;The End of Power,&quot; a remarkable new book by the remarkable Moises Naim, the former editor of Foreign Policy....]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/feeling_powerless_all_around_119742.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119742</guid>
					<author>Richard Cohen</author>					
					<category>Richard Cohen</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 06:44:56 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Vice President Julian Castro?</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ SAN ANTONIO, Texas -- Close your eyes for a moment and imagine it&apos;s the summer of 2016. Fresh off her victory in the primaries, presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Hillary Clinton is searching for a running mate.
If the 68-year-old Clinton of three years from now were to play the role of Dr. Frankenstein in crafting the politically ideal VP pick, relative youth likely would be a key trait in order to balance the ticket.
And, perhaps facing a general election campaign against the first Hispanic presidential or vice-presidential nominee (think Marco Rubio, Ted Cruz, or Susana...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/vice_president_julian_castro_119737.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119737</guid>
					<author>Scott Conroy</author>					
					<category>Scott Conroy</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 05:51:02 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204305_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="158" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204305_3_.jpg" height="57" width="90" />
						<media:title>204305</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>&quot;I Have a Dream&quot;</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ On 28 August, 1963, Martin Luther King delivered his iconic &quot;I have a dream speech&quot; on the steps of the Lincoln Memorial in Washington. Below is the full text of his speech.
I am happy to join with you today in what will go down in history as the greatest demonstration for freedom in the history of our nation.
Five score years ago, a great American, in whose symbolic shadow we stand signed the Emancipation Proclamation. This momentous decree came as a great beacon light of hope to millions of Negro slaves who had been seared in the flames of withering injustice. It came as a joyous...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/i_have_a_dream_119739.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119739</guid>
					<author>Martin Luther King Jr.</author>					
					<category>Martin Luther King Jr.</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 05:41:59 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Will U.S. Attack Syria? A Primer on the Rationale</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ The Obama administration stood poised Tuesday to attack Syria within days, setting off anxieties that stretched from Damascus to Wall Street.
Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel, traveling in Indonesia, said U.S. military forces are ready to carry out the commander-in-chief&amp;rsquo;s orders, working off plans the Pentagon presented to President Obama over the weekend. At a news conference, Hagel suggested pending intelligence would bolster the administration&amp;rsquo;s decision-making. &amp;ldquo;Until we get all the facts and we&apos;re absolutely confident of what happened in Syria, I&apos;m...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/will_us_attack_syria_a_primer_on_the_rationale_119738.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119738</guid>
					<author>Alexis Simendinger</author>					
					<category>Alexis Simendinger</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 05:28:46 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204314_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="206" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204314_3_.jpg" height="74" width="90" />
						<media:title>204314</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Colorado&#039;s Grassroots Revolt Against Gun-Grabbers</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ COLORADO SPRINGS -- While most Americans will be chillin&apos; out, maxin&apos; and relaxin&apos; this Labor Day weekend, dedicated patriots in Colorado are hard at work preparing for a groundbreaking special election day with nationwide repercussions. George Washington would be proud.
On September 10, Democratic legislator and state Senate President John Morse of Colorado Springs faces a citizen recall for his sellout to New York anti-gun special interests, for his betrayal of transparency and accountability to constituents, and for his destructive economic policies that are driving...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/colorados_grassroots_revolt_against_gun-grabbers_119733.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119733</guid>
					<author>Michelle Malkin</author>					
					<category>Michelle Malkin</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 04:43:34 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>It&#039;s Time for Obama to Act Forcefully on Syria</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Bashar al-Assad&amp;rsquo;s latest use of chemical weapons against his own civilians seems to have finally provoked President Obama into taking action against the Syrian regime. Until now, the administration&amp;rsquo;s response had been confined to stern denunciations, entreating Vladimir Putin to behave as if he gives a damn about &amp;ldquo;our common humanity,&amp;rdquo; as Secretary of State John Kerry put it, and promising small arms to Syrian rebels that never quite materialized.
Obama is moving with unusual (for him) alacrity to assert the regime&amp;rsquo;s culpability in the attack...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/its_time_for_obama_to_act_forcefully_on_syria_119732.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119732</guid>
					<author>Mark Salter</author>					
					<category>Mark Salter</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 04:41:10 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203549_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="182" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203549_3_.jpg" height="66" width="90" />
						<media:title>203549</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Trains to Nowhere</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ When Democrats and Republicans agree, I get nervous. It often means that they agree to grab my wallet.Both parties now agree that we don&apos;t have extra budget money lying around, but both say government does need to spend more on &quot;infrastructure.&quot;
Even conservatives want more spent on roads and mass transit.
The reason, advocates claim, is that infrastructure, unlike most government spending, has a &quot;multiplier effect&quot; -- it creates new wealth by doing things like speeding up travel.
Well, it might.
Advocates also point out something that seems obvious to them:...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/trains_to_nowhere_119735.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119735</guid>
					<author>John Stossel</author>					
					<category>John Stossel</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 22:20:26 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Ginsburg on the Offensive</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ WASHINGTON -- Maybe it&apos;s good that the justices have another month off before the Supreme Court starts up again. The wounds from last term don&apos;t seem fully healed.
There was Justice Antonin Scalia, speaking in Montana last week, none too subtly chastising his colleagues&apos; rulings on gay rights. &quot;It&apos;s not up to the courts to invent new minorities that get special protections,&quot; Scalia said, according to The Associated Press.
Asked about the most wrenching decision in his time on the bench, Scalia replied, &quot;Well, is Obamacare too recent?&quot; Which suggests...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/ginsburg_on_the_offensive_119736.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119736</guid>
					<author>Ruth Marcus</author>					
					<category>Ruth Marcus</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 19:10:50 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203878_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="167" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203878_3_.jpg" height="60" width="90" />
						<media:title>203878</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Fixing the NSA: We Need an NSA Special Prosecutor</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Serious Republican conservatives are finally understanding that we must rein in the NSA and correct the abuses which have been exposed by Edward Snowden and by news reporting ever since. These hawks -- men like Senators Lindsay Graham, R-S.C., and Jim Inhofe, R-Okla. -- know that we need the NSA to continue to be effective in countering terrorism but that, to preserve that mandate in a democracy, it has to be restrained and reformed.
The answer is not new rules or restrictions. No policy can anticipate either the exigencies of what we must do to uncover terrorist plots that threaten us or, on...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/28/fixing_the_nsa_we_need_an_nsa_special_prosecutor__119734.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119734</guid>
					<author>Dick Morris</author>					
					<category>Dick Morris</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/28/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 19:06:14 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Obama Administration: Its Incompetence Is Historic</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Evidence of the astonishing incompetence of the Obama administration continues to roll in.
It started with the stimulus package. One-third of the money went to public employee union members -- a political payoff not very stimulating to anyone else. Billions went to green energy loans, like the $500 million that the government lost in backing the obviously hapless Solyndra.
Infrastructure projects, which the president continues to tout, never seem to get built. He&apos;s been talking about dredging the port of Charleston, for example, to accommodate the big container ships coming in when the...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/obama_could_learn_from_fdr_on_how_to_get_things_done_119722.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119722</guid>
					<author>Michael Barone</author>					
					<category>Michael Barone</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 04:03:05 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Credibility over &quot;Red Lines&quot; No Reason for War</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Support is gathering in Washington for military action in Syria. The rationale is as follows: Evidence that Bashar al-Assad&amp;rsquo;s forces used chemical weapons means President Obama&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;red line&amp;rdquo; has been crossed, and the U.S. must prove its credibility on the international stage by responding. In addition, we&amp;rsquo;re told, humanitarianism compels us to defend the rebels and their supporters from the Syrian government&amp;rsquo;s forces.
Neither argument is a good reason to launch cruise missiles, airstrikes or any other sort of war.
U.S. leaders obsess...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/credibility_over_red_lines_no_reason_for_war_119730.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119730</guid>
					<author>Benjamin Friedman</author>					
					<category>Benjamin Friedman</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 12:51:15 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204043_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="185" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204043_3_.jpg" height="67" width="90" />
						<media:title>204043</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>The Dream Derailed</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Fifty years ago, Martin Luther King Jr. delivered his &amp;ldquo;I have a dream&amp;rdquo; speech at the Lincoln Memorial to a crowd of over 200,000 people. The crowd had gathered to protest the dangerous state into which race relations had fallen in the summer of 1963. King&amp;rsquo;s memorable speech was part of &amp;ldquo;the March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom,&amp;rdquo; and its solemn cadences ring as powerfully today they did 50 years ago. No one who heard it could forget its immensely powerful assault on segregation, the demise of which no respectable person&amp;mdash;northerner...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/the_dream_derailed_119729.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119729</guid>
					<author>Richard Epstein</author>					
					<category>Richard Epstein</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 12:46:07 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204258_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="177" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204258_3_.jpg" height="64" width="90" />
						<media:title>204258</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Long-Term Strategy Needed to End the War in Syria</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Although I believe that President Barack Obama has taken too long to offer meaningful help to the Syrian opposition over the past two years, a policy that has permitted President Bashar Assad to remain in power too long while it facilitated the rise of extremist insurgent groups, I also sympathize with the White House&amp;rsquo;s apparent reluctance to engage in that country&amp;rsquo;s terrible civil war, even at this juncture.
On balance, the United States should retaliate against the Syrian regime. Presidential credibility is on the line, given that last year Obama called the possible use...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/long-term_strategy_needed_to_end_the_war_in_syria_119731.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119731</guid>
					<author>Michael O'Hanlon</author>					
					<category>Michael O'Hanlon</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 12:42:07 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204257_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="206" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204257_3_.jpg" height="74" width="90" />
						<media:title>204257</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>One of These Embargoes Is Not Like the Other</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Let&amp;rsquo;s play a game. Here are five countries, see if you can tell what they have in common, and more importantly, how they differ:
1. Iran2. North Korea3. Syria4. Sudan5. Cuba
The answer is simple: all of these countries are under either a comprehensive or partial U.S. trade embargo, but one of them shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be; namely, Cuba. The first four countries are, undeniably, a source of great anxiety and should be under an embargo.
Iranian president Ahmadinejad was an uncontrollable bully intent on making and using nuclear weapons. President Rouhani presents a much less...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/one_of_these_embargoes_is_not_like_the_other_119728.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119728</guid>
					<author>Marla Goodman</author>					
					<category>Marla Goodman</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 12:13:41 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>The March on Washington&#039;s Little-Sung Hero</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Tomorrow, President Obama will lead the list of luminaries speaking on the 50th anniversary of the March on Washington. Today, the president and Secretary of State John Kerry continue their round of phone calls to foreign counterparts, apparently in preparation for U.S. military action against Syria.
Those two events&amp;mdash;a commemoration of a milestone in American history and armed conflict in the Middle East&amp;mdash;are not directly related. But this week&amp;rsquo;s events, as well as the life&amp;rsquo;s work of an American original named Bayard Rustin, remind us that the cause of...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/the_march_on_washingtons_little-sung_hero_119726.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119726</guid>
					<author>Carl M. Cannon</author>					
					<category>Carl M. Cannon</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 11:19:27 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204251_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="158" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204251_3_.jpg" height="57" width="90" />
						<media:title>204251</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Obama Cannot Rise Above Politics</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ It&apos;s ironic that President Obama so often carps about politics -- blaming &quot;politics as usual&quot; or &quot;hyperpartisanship&quot; for everything from the lack of economic growth to joblessness to climate change -- when he is the most relentlessly partisan president in recent memory. Obama is a staunch left/liberal who finds it very difficult to rise above politics and attempt to unite the country. Arguably, his very best speech, the one delivered in Tucson after the Gabby Giffords shooting, did transcend partisanship. It was an outlier.
The president inserted himself into the...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/obama_cannot_rise_above_politics_119718.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119718</guid>
					<author>Mona Charen</author>					
					<category>Mona Charen</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 22:22:19 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>We All Need Moderate Republicans</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Moderate Republicans are, were, good things. I use the past tense &quot;were&quot; because as they became rarities, the centrists&apos; chief function was preserving majorities in Congress for their radicalized party.
New England used to send lots of moderate Republicans to Washington. No more, and it&apos;s not because there aren&apos;t attractive Republican candidates. It&apos;s because the ones representing liberal-to-moderate regions became scapegoats at which party extremists directed their primal screams.
There arose the stupid &quot;RINO (Republican in name only) Hunters Club,&quot;...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/we_all_need_moderate_republicans_119715.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119715</guid>
					<author>Froma Harrop</author>					
					<category>Froma Harrop</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 22:13:16 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Tolerance, Health and Fascism</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ I cannot count the number of times I heard liberal professors and liberal writers quote the phrase: &quot;When fascism comes to America, it will be wrapped in the flag and carrying a cross.&quot;
The phrase is brilliant. There is actually no threat to America of fascism coming from the right. The essence of the American right, after all, is less government; and fascism, by definition, demands ever larger government.
Therefore, if there is a real fascist threat to America, it comes from the left, whose appetite for state power is essentially unlimited. But because the left has so long...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/tolerance_health_and_fascism_119725.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119725</guid>
					<author>Dennis Prager</author>					
					<category>Dennis Prager</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 20:27:10 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Obama Mulling Response to WMD Use in Syria</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ President Obama worked Monday to muster a coordinated international response to retaliate against Syria&amp;rsquo;s apparent deadly use of chemical weapons near Damascus on Aug. 21.
Faced with video evidence and some first-person accounts of lethal gassing, and under renewed pressure to react, the president weighed options as Syria&amp;rsquo;s more than two-year-old civil war crossed the &amp;ldquo;red line&amp;rdquo; Obama laid out a year ago.
&amp;ldquo;President Obama believes there must be accountability,&amp;rdquo; and will decide on &amp;ldquo;an informed response,&amp;rdquo; Secretary...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/obama_mulling_response_to_wmd_use_in_syria_119724.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119724</guid>
					<author>Alexis Simendinger</author>					
					<category>Alexis Simendinger</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 19:12:57 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204043_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="185" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204043_3_.jpg" height="67" width="90" />
						<media:title>204043</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Listen to the Doctor: Weed Really Can Heal</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ CNN&apos;s Dr. Sanjay Gupta admitted earlier this month that he had been wrong in his opposition to medical marijuana during the rollout for his documentary &quot;Weed.&quot; Gupta reported on research that demonstrated the proven benefits of marijuana in treating neuropathic pain. Medical marijuana was the only drug that helped a 5-year-old girl with Dravet syndrome live without constant seizures. It calmed the constant hiccuping of a 19-year-old. Israelis use it to treat Parkinson&apos;s disease and other ailments.
Gupta took on the federal government&apos;s classification of marijuana as a...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/listen_to_the_doctor_weed_really_can_heal_119723.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119723</guid>
					<author>Debra Saunders</author>					
					<category>Debra Saunders</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 17:07:19 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>A Poignant Anniversary</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ The 50th anniversary of the March on Washington, and of the Reverend Martin Luther King&apos;s memorable &quot;I have a dream&quot; speech, is a time for reflections -- some inspiring, and some painful and ominous.
At the core of Dr. King&apos;s speech was his dream of a world in which people would not be judged by the color of their skin, but by &quot;the content of their character.&quot;
Judging individuals by their individual character is at the opposite pole from judging how groups are statistically represented among employees, college students or political figures.
Yet many -- if not...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/a_poignant_anniversary_119721.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119721</guid>
					<author>Thomas Sowell</author>					
					<category>Thomas Sowell</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 16:56:31 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>A Truly Great Phony</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Many years ago, I was a member of a committee that was recommending to whom grant money should be awarded. Since I knew one of the applicants, I asked if this meant that I should recuse myself from voting on his application.
&quot;No,&quot; the chairman said. &quot;I know him too -- and he is one of the truly great phonies of our time.&quot;
The man was indeed a very talented phony. He could convince almost anybody of almost anything -- provided that they were not already knowledgeable about the subject.
He had once spoken to me very authoritatively about Marxian economics, apparently unaware...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/a_truly_great_phony_119720.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119720</guid>
					<author>Thomas Sowell</author>					
					<category>Thomas Sowell</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 16:54:58 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Outside Syria, Difficult Adjustments</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ ZAATRI REFUGEE CAMP, Jordan -- I ask a Syrian refugee named Isra why her 8-year-old boy isn&apos;t attending the camp school. &quot;He doesn&apos;t like school,&quot; she explains. At home in Daraa, an agent of the regime came into his second-grade classroom, forced her son to hold a grenade against his chest and told him, &quot;Go home to your father. Tell him if he doesn&apos;t stop fighting for the Free Syrian Army, I will come back next week and pull the pin.&quot;It is a hint of the brutality just across the border, largely hidden from view. When the terror and killing finally calm, one...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/outside_syria_difficult_adjustments_119719.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119719</guid>
					<author>Michael Gerson</author>					
					<category>Michael Gerson</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 16:52:25 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Assad Must Be Punished</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ WASHINGTON -- History says don&apos;t do it. Most Americans say don&apos;t do it. But President Obama has to punish Syrian dictator Bashar al-Assad&apos;s homicidal regime with a military strike -- and hope that history and the people are wrong.
If it is true that the regime killed hundreds of civilians with nerve gas in a Damascus suburb last week -- and U.S. officials say there is &quot;very little doubt&quot; -- then Obama has no choice. The use of chemical weapons cannot be tolerated, and any government or group that does so must be made to suffer real consequences. Obama should uphold...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/assad_must_be_punished_119717.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119717</guid>
					<author>Eugene Robinson</author>					
					<category>Eugene Robinson</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 16:49:34 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Congress Should Veto Obama&#039;s War</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ &quot;Congress doesn&apos;t have a whole lot of core responsibilities,&quot; said Barack Obama last week in an astonishing remark.
For in the Constitution, Congress appears as the first branch of government. And among its enumerated powers are the power to tax, coin money, create courts, provide for the common defense, raise and support an army, maintain a navy and declare war.
But, then, perhaps Obama&apos;s contempt is justified.
For consider Congress&apos; broad assent to news that Obama has decided to attack Syria, a nation that has not attacked us and against which Congress has never...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/27/congress_should_veto_obamas_war_119716.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119716</guid>
					<author>Pat Buchanan</author>					
					<category>Pat Buchanan</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/27/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 16:44:31 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>The March on Washington Was 22 Years in the Making</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ On Wednesday, President Obama will speak at a 50th anniversary commemoration of the 1963 civil rights march on Washington. He will not be the only speaker, any more than the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. was the only speaker on August 28, 1963.
Today, the shorthand for that great event is King&amp;rsquo;s soaring &amp;ldquo;I Have a Dream Speech.&amp;rdquo; But although the good reverend was the civil rights movement&amp;rsquo;s most eloquent spokesman, he was not the organizer of that march, which was 22 years in the making.
On August 20, 1963, at the 60th news conference of his presidency(!),...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/the_march_on_washington_was_22_years_in_the_making.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119714</guid>
					<author>Carl M. Cannon</author>					
					<category>Carl M. Cannon</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 16:16:31 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204032_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="149" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/204032_3_.jpg" height="54" width="90" />
						<media:title>204032</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Kurtz&#039;s FOX News Show to Debut Sept. 8</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Howard Kurtz&apos;s new show, &quot;MediaBuzz,&quot; will debut on the FOX News Channel on Sunday, Sept. 8, at 11 a.m. Eastern time, the network announced Monday.
Kurtz, a veteran media reporter, hosted &quot;Reliable Sources&quot; on CNN from 1998 until this past June. He has also worked as Washington bureau chief for The Daily Beast and Newsweek. Before that, he was at The Washington Post for 29 years.
The new show will focus on the news media, its role in politics and the growth of social media. Kurtz will also explore media bias, according to FOX News.
Lauren Ashburn, the editor in chief...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/howard_kurtzs_fox_news_show_to_debut_sept_8.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119713</guid>
					<author>Tim Hains</author>					
					<category>Tim Hains</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 15:29:46 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>10 Years After California&#039;s Recall, Lessons Learned</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Now that San Diego Mayor Bob Filner plans to call it quits&amp;nbsp;this Friday, &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s Finest City&amp;rdquo; will hold&amp;nbsp;a special election&amp;nbsp;(sometime before the end of November) to determine his successor.
Rest assured, that election will be &amp;ldquo;special&amp;rdquo; in name only. Most of the Democratic and Republican names being bandied about fall into one of two categories: current officeholders or past officeholders. Barring the unforeseen, San Diegans won&amp;rsquo;t have the choice of a political outsider to help rejuvenate a city whose...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/10_years_after_californias_recall_lessons_learned_119712.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119712</guid>
					<author>Bill Whalen</author>					
					<category>Bill Whalen</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 11:38:28 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Biden&#039;s Uphill Road to 2016</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ His Republican foes branded it the &amp;ldquo;2016 Kickoff Tour&amp;rdquo; and vice-president Joe Biden made it clear to the people of &amp;ldquo;my native town, Scranton&amp;rdquo; that he hopes to build a White House campaign on tales of his humble upbringing in Pennsylvania coal country.
After recently seeming to bolster former secretary of state Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s credentials to be his successor, President Barack Obama went out of his way to give a boost to his No 2.
Their joint appearance on Friday was also significant because coming from a place such as Scranton, an archetype...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/bidens_uphill_road_to_2016_119710.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119710</guid>
					<author>Toby Harnden</author>					
					<category>Toby Harnden</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 06:24:25 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203961_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="167" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203961_3_.jpg" height="60" width="90" />
						<media:title>203961</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>The Digital Threat to the Political Class</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ You might expect a story about wine, The Washington Post, Twitter and polling to be about the lifestyle of the nation&apos;s political elite. But this one is about the digital threat to America&apos;s Political Class.
Let&apos;s start with the wine. A recent story on Marketwatch.com noted that apps are now available to scan the label of a wine bottle, compare prices and order online. Other apps help people learn more about wine and make restaurant recommendations. One wine director complained, &quot;Wine is an experience and should not be sold that way.&quot; But 6 percent of wine sales last...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/the_digital_threat_to_the_political_class_119700.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119700</guid>
					<author>Scott Rasmussen</author>					
					<category>Scott Rasmussen</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 21:51:25 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Britain Gives America a Preview of Obamacare</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ PORTSTEWART, Northern Ireland &amp;mdash; Each visit to the United Kingdom brings new horror stories about the National Health Service.
Last month, Sir Bruce Keogh, medical director of the NHS, issued a forensic report, commissioned by the government, which found that 14 underperforming hospitals in England had substandard care, contributing to the needless deaths of nearly 13,000 people since 2005.
Earlier this year, it was reported that a single hospital in Staffordshire recorded 1,400 &quot;excess&quot; deaths.
Following the July report, letters from patients and relatives of those who...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/britain_gives_america_a_preview_of_obamacare_119701.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119701</guid>
					<author>Cal Thomas</author>					
					<category>Cal Thomas</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 21:51:19 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>The Armageddon Caucus</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ WASHINGTON -- Are you ready for the Big Magilla of American politics? This fall, every important domestic issue could crash into every other: health care reform, autopilot budget cuts, a government shutdown, even a default on the national debt.
If I were betting, I&apos;d wager we will somehow avoid a total meltdown. House Speaker John Boehner seems desperate to get around his party&apos;s Armageddon Caucus.
But after three years of congressional dysfunction brought on by the rise of a radicalized brand of conservatism, it&apos;s time to call the core questions:
Will our ability to govern...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/the_armageddon_caucus_119707.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119707</guid>
					<author>E.J. Dionne</author>					
					<category>E.J. Dionne</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 21:46:50 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Grading Obama&#039;s College-Ranking Proposal</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ SYRACUSE, N.Y. -- President Obama and I both spent Thursday and Friday rallying college students in upstate New York. We weren&amp;rsquo;t doing this activity together; he was macro, I was micro. My job was helping move a daughter into the dorm for her freshman year at Syracuse University. Obama was trying to ensure that more American students can attend the school that best helps them realize their dreams&amp;mdash;without amassing an untenable mountain of debt.
I&amp;rsquo;m pulling for the president in this endeavor. Syracuse seems terrific, and the right place for our kid. But it is...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/grading_obamas_college-ranking_proposal_119709.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119709</guid>
					<author>Carl M. Cannon</author>					
					<category>Carl M. Cannon</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 21:43:52 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203917_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="145" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203917_3_.jpg" height="52" width="90" />
						<media:title>203917</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>The Battle for the Fed</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ WASHINGTON -- Was this necessary?
The struggle to succeed Ben Bernanke as chairman of the Federal Reserve has turned into a soap opera. Bernanke, it is widely assumed, has told President Obama that he doesn&apos;t want a third four-year term -- or has been informed that he won&apos;t be reappointed. This has triggered a highly public campaign by partisans of the two leading contenders for the job: Lawrence Summers, ex-treasury secretary (in the Clinton years) and former Harvard president; and Janet Yellen, the Fed&apos;s present vice chairman. Both are economists.
Summers, say his fans in...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/26/the_battle_for_the_fed_119708.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119708</guid>
					<author>Robert Samuelson</author>					
					<category>Robert Samuelson</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/26/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 21:39:57 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Prison Hunger Strike a Dangerous Game</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Here&apos;s how you know the California prison inmate hunger strike is a stunt, if a dangerous stunt: The strike to protest security housing units in California prisons began with 30,000 participants; Jay Leno, Susan Sarandon and other celebrities signed a letter that denounced the SHU as &quot;solitary confinement&quot; and &quot;torture.&quot; As of Thursday, the count was down to 79 inmates, including 44 who had fasted continuously.
Days after U.S. District Judge Thelton Henderson signed an order authorizing prison doctors to force-feed inmates, the Prisoner Hunger Strike Solidarity...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/25/prison_hunger_strike_a_dangerous_game_119706.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119706</guid>
					<author>Debra Saunders</author>					
					<category>Debra Saunders</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/25/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 11:18:28 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>On the Farm, Making Room for Pigs</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ DEKALB, Ill. -- The placid cornfields of the upper Midwest have the look of a place where nothing important ever changes. But here, at a large pig farm five miles south of town, the beginnings of a small revolution are unmistakable.
My host today is Bob Johnson, a sturdy 6-footer who gives the impression he would not be rushed if he were running with the bulls in Pamplona. As president of Johnson-Pate Pork Inc., which he co-owns with two sisters and a brother-in-law, he has taken a big role in changing the way hogs are handled.
In recent years, one major food corporation after another, from...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/25/on_the_farm_making_room_for_pigs_119705.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119705</guid>
					<author>Steve Chapman</author>					
					<category>Steve Chapman</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/25/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 11:17:38 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Q&amp;A: Bolling Isn&#039;t Bullish on Va. Gov. Candidates</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Since scratching his own Virginia gubernatorial bid last year, Lt. Gov. Bill Bolling has come to think of himself as something of a quiet referee in the contentious race between Republican Attorney General Ken Cuccinelli and Democrat Terry McAuliffe, a former DNC chairman. Bolling, who has no preferred player in the match-up, largely stays on the sidelines. But some news in state politics this week put a bit of the spotlight on how Bolling would react to those developments: Gov. Bob McDonnell met with prosecutors looking into his relationship with a donor, Star Scientific CEO Jonnie Williams;...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/25/qa_bolling_isnt_bullish_on_va_gov_candidates_119697.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119697</guid>
					<author>Caitlin Huey-Burns</author>					
					<category>Caitlin Huey-Burns</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/25/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:53:28 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203677_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="148" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203677_3_.jpg" height="53" width="90" />
						<media:title>203677</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>U.S. Forces Move Closer to Syria as Obama Weighs Options</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ WASHINGTON (AP) -- U.S. naval forces are moving closer to Syria as President Barack Obama considers military options for responding to the alleged use of chemical weapons by the Assad government. The president emphasized that a quick intervention in the Syrian civil war was problematic, given the international considerations that should precede a military strike.
The White House said the president would meet Saturday with his national security team to consider possible next steps by the United States. Officials say once the facts are clear, Obama will make a decision about how to...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/24/us_forces_move_closer_to_syria_as_obama_weighs_options_119704.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119704</guid>
					<author>Bradley Klapper and Robert Burns</author>					
					<category>Bradley Klapper and Robert Burns</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/24/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 08:36:39 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203806_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="156" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203806_3_.jpg" height="56" width="90" />
						<media:title>203806</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Resetting U.S. Foreign Policy</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Aside from the carnage in Benghazi, the most enduring image from Hillary Clinton&apos;s tenure as US secretary of state was the fake remote control she brought with her to Moscow in 2009 with the word &quot;Reset&quot; in misspelled Russian embossed on it.
Clinton&apos;s gimmick was meant to show that under President Barack Obama, American foreign policy would be fundamentally transformed. Since Obama and Clinton blamed much of the world&apos;s troubles on the misdeeds of their country, under their stewardship of US foreign policy, the US would reset everything.
Around the globe, all bets...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/24/resetting_us_foreign_policy_119703.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119703</guid>
					<author>Caroline Glick</author>					
					<category>Caroline Glick</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/24/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 08:31:17 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Geithner to the Rescue?</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ When it comes to Fed policy, one of the hottest topics on Wall Street is the next Fed chair. Who will replace Ben Bernanke? And believe it or not, Timothy Geithner&apos;s name may be resurfacing. Is it possible that the former treasury secretary will come to the rescue of a leaderless and hopelessly divided central bank that has no real clue where it&apos;s going or how fast it should get there?
Wait a second ...&amp;nbsp;Geithner?&amp;nbsp;Did someone say Geithner?&amp;nbsp;We thought he retired from government to go home to New York.
Well yes, but not exactly.
A key insider source tells me...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/24/geithner_to_the_rescue_119702.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119702</guid>
					<author>Larry Kudlow</author>					
					<category>Larry Kudlow</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/24/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 05:41:19 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Is Obama Good for Black Americans?</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Buried in a New York Times story about the economy was this arresting statistic: Median family income for black Americans has declined a whopping 10.9 percent during the Obama administration. It has declined for other groups as well -- 3.6 percent for non-Hispanic whites and 4.5 percent for Hispanics - but the figure for blacks is huge. This decline does not include losses suffered during the financial crisis and the recession that followed, but it instead measures declines since June 2009, when the recession officially ended.
That&apos;s not the only bad news for African-Americans. The...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/is_obama_good_for_black_americans_119685.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119685</guid>
					<author>Mona Charen</author>					
					<category>Mona Charen</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 05:31:06 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Obama Troubled by Syrian Report, But Still Cautious</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ President Obama said available information about an alleged mass chemical attack in Syria -- which may have killed more than 1,000 people -- moves beyond civil war and into &amp;ldquo;core&amp;rdquo; U.S. national interests in the use or transport of weapons of mass destruction.
During a CNN interview broadcast Friday, the president said the deaths, including of children, reported in graphic detail this week are of &amp;ldquo;grave concern&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;very troublesome.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I think it is fair to say that as difficult as the problem is, this is something that is...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/obama_troubled_by_syrian_report_but_still_cautious_119699.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119699</guid>
					<author>Alexis Simendinger</author>					
					<category>Alexis Simendinger</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 14:33:25 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203702_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="184" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203702_3_.jpg" height="66" width="90" />
						<media:title>203702</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Soldier Guilty of Murder for Fort Hood Shootings</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ FORT HOOD, Texas (AP) -- Army Maj. Nidal Hasan was convicted Friday in the 2009 shooting rampage at Fort Hood, a shocking assault against American troops at home by one of their own who said he opened fire on fellow soldiers to protect Muslim insurgents abroad.
The Army psychiatrist acknowledged carrying out the attack in a crowded waiting room where unarmed troops were making final preparations to deploy to Afghanistan and Iraq. Thirteen people were killed and more than 30 wounded.
Because Hasan never denied his actions, the court-martial was always less about a conviction than it was about...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/soldier_guilty_of_murder_for_fort_hood_shootings_119698.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119698</guid>
					<author>Will Weissert and Paul Weber</author>					
					<category>Will Weissert and Paul Weber</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 13:09:00 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203688_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="174" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203688_3_.jpg" height="63" width="90" />
						<media:title>203688</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>The U.S. Can Afford to Rethink Aid to Egypt</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ In the aftermath of the&amp;nbsp;Egyptian military&amp;rsquo;s brutal crackdown&amp;nbsp;on&amp;nbsp;Muslim Brotherhood supporters, many have suggested that the United States must nevertheless sustain most or all of its&amp;nbsp;$1.5 billion in annual aid to Egypt because of our military dependence on the Suez Canal and Egyptian airspace. While these geographical features of the Arab world&amp;rsquo;s central state are desirable and convenient for U.S. national security interests in the broader Middle East, and while there are other reasons not to categorically cut off contact with the...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/the_us_can_afford_to_rethink_aid_to_egypt_119696.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119696</guid>
					<author>Michael O'Hanlon</author>					
					<category>Michael O'Hanlon</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:18:15 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Egypt Goes From Bad to Worse</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ The Egyptian military has overthrown the country&amp;rsquo;s first elected President, held him incommunicado and without benefit of legal proceedings, killed over a thousand of its people, labeled as terrorists the political party that received more than half the votes in parliamentary and presidential elections, and have declared a state of emergency, authorizing use of deadly force against civilians. They have suspended judicial oversight, arrested hundreds of Muslim Brotherhood leaders, killed Brotherhood prisoners in captivity, released former President Mubarak showing the courts to be...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/egypt_goes_from_bad_to_worse_119695.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119695</guid>
					<author>Kori Schake</author>					
					<category>Kori Schake</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:06:39 -0500</pubDate><media:content url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203671_1_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" height="169" width="250" />
						<media:thumbnail url="http://images.rcp.realclearpolitics.com/203671_3_.jpg" height="61" width="90" />
						<media:title>203671</media:title></item>
				<item>
					<title>Why Egypt Has Coups and We Don&#039;t</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Why does Egypt burn and America remains peaceful? Tunku Varadarajan on what the stark contrast in transfers of power reveal about each country&amp;mdash;even when the U.S. is at its most tense, like during Bush v. Gore.
The hideous events in Egypt make me ask (even as I shudder) how that country will ever settle back into a state of un-murderous co-existence. Can the savagery be forgotten? Is there any hope for political reconciliation? Actually, forget hope: Is there any mechanism for reconciliation? How on earth do you bring warring sides together when there is no national institution that...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/why_egypt_has_coups_and_we_dont.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119694</guid>
					<author>Tunku Varadarajan</author>					
					<category>Tunku Varadarajan</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:00:53 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>MSNBC Has Full Deck of Race Cards</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ &quot;Why do they seem so determined to also make it racial?&amp;rdquo;
So asks Joy-Ann Reid, the managing editor of The Grio, a web magazine owned by NBC News whose mission is to &amp;ldquo;focus on news and events that have a unique interest and/or pronounced impact within the national African Americans audience.&amp;rdquo; The &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rdquo; in question are conservatives and journalists asking, among other things, why President Obama hasn&amp;rsquo;t inserted himself into a new criminal-justice case the way he did in the Trayvon Martin tragedy.&amp;nbsp;
The irony-impaired Reid...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/msnbc_has_full_deck_of_race_cards_119693.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119693</guid>
					<author>Jonah Goldberg</author>					
					<category>Jonah Goldberg</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 07:12:44 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>Stop and Frisk Doesn&#039;t Target Minorities, It Protects Them</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ New York City seems on the verge of making the same mistake that Detroit made 40 years ago. The mistake is to abolish the NYPD practice referred to as stop and frisk.
It&apos;s more accurately called stop, question and frisk. People were stopped and questioned 4.4 million times between 2004 and 2012. But the large majority were not frisked.
The effectiveness of this police practice, initiated by Mayor Rudy Giuliani in 1994 and continued by Mayor Michael Bloomberg, is not in doubt. The number of homicides -- the most accurately measured crime -- in New York fell from a peak of 2,605 in 1990 to...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/stop_and_frisk_doesnt_target_minorities_it_protects_them_119690.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119690</guid>
					<author>Michael Barone</author>					
					<category>Michael Barone</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 06:39:25 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>How Oberlin Manufactured the Hate-Crime Hoax of the Year</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ Busted. Stone-cold busted. Just as I suspected, &quot;progressive&quot; pranksters at Oberlin College have been definitively unmasked as the perpetrators of phony campus &quot;hate crimes&quot; that scored international headlines in March. The blabbermouth academic administrators who helped fuel the hysteria are now running for cover.
The Associated Press, The New York Times, MSNBC, Yahoo News and the Huffington Post were among the media outlets that trumpeted the story of supposed racism, homophobia and anti-Semitism run amok at my alma mater. Throughout the winter, anti-black and anti-gay...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/how_oberlin_manufactured_the_hate-crime_hoax_of_the_year_119692.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119692</guid>
					<author>Michelle Malkin</author>					
					<category>Michelle Malkin</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 06:28:52 -0500</pubDate></item>
				<item>
					<title>A Troubling Pattern</title>
                                   <subtitle><![CDATA[]]></subtitle>
					<description><![CDATA[ WASHINGTON -- Footnote 14 should scare every American. Even the parts that aren&apos;t blacked out.
The footnote is contained in the just-declassified 2011 opinion by U.S. District Judge John Bates, then the chief judge of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court.
In the ruling, Bates found that the government had been sweeping up emails before receiving court approval in 2008 and even after that was illegally collecting &quot;tens of thousands of wholly domestic communications.&quot;
That&apos;s not the really scary part. This is: &quot;The court is troubled that the government&apos;s...]]></description>
					<link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/08/23/a_troubling_pattern_119687.html</link>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">200119687</guid>
					<author>Ruth Marcus</author>					
					<category>Ruth Marcus</category>
					<pubdate>2013/08</pubdate>
					<fullpubdate>08/23/2013/00/00/00</fullpubdate>
                              <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 06:06:47 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>